Guide to the Gathering of the Tribes Archive 1983-2006 MSS.198
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Media
  - Subseries A: Video
    - W.C. Fields / 3 Classics, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Video Treasures, Inc.). (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0253)
    - "Watch Me", circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0054)
    - Works on Paper: Star Black, circa 1983-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0009)
    - Lavinia Williams, Lecture Demonstration, St. Peter's Church, 1983; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0146)
    - Mona Lisa, 1985; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial Release (HBO Cannon Video).; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0118)
    - Ishmael Reed: Hollywood's War on Ethnic America, Part 1 of 2, January 8 1987; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Copy".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0187)
    - Ishmael Reed: Hollywood's War on Ethnic America, Part 2 of 2, January 8 1987; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0314)
    - Prince: Sign O' the Times, 1987; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:25:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0039)
    - Black Classic - 2-9-89 & 2-16-89 / Miles Davis / Art Blakey / Wynton Marsalis / Will Women Sing the Blues, circa February 1989; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0190)
    - Steve BET - 3/9/89 / The Last Emperor / Jazz Show / ? BET - 3/16/89 / School [Dune] / BET -3/24/89, March 1989; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 08:34:00; Label annotations: Pt 1 - "1 hr"; Pt 2 - "2 hr. 40 min"; Pt 3 "1 hr"; Pt 4 "1 hr"; Pt 5 "1 hr. 54 min"; Pt 6 "1 hr"; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0172)
    - [Unknown], July 15 1989; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0296)
    - [Unknown], August 24 1989; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0197)
    - Sunday August 20th / Sunday August 26, circa 1989-2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0177)
    - Ishmael Reed 62590 Mosaic Books / 8316 - Patient - JF - 6-30-90 DG., June 1990; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0188)
    - Smokin' Word '90, 1990; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:40:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0021)
    - Last Crack: Burning Time, March 7 1991; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:17:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0034)
    - Poetry Reading, Prof. Cannon, April 17 1991; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0184)
    - The House of Johnson - The Living Theatre, October 27 1991; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 197.0175)
    - The Set Up, by Steve Cannon, Nuyorican Poets' Cafe - Music Added, May 13 & 29 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0095)
    - The Set Up, May 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotations: "5-13-92 - No Music. 5-29-92 - Music Added. No sucrose 'Steve Flubs' for Chump Intro." (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0028)
    - Chump Change, October 3 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label Annotations: "By Steve Cannon, At Dixon Place"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0043)
    - No Sucrose Intro / Chump Change, October 31 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0120)
    - En Vogue, Whitney 11-10-92, Skep 11-17 / Tribes Interview 10-21-93, November 10 & 17 1992, October 21 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0090)
    - Nuyorican - 1st Poet's Choir / Slam, December 18 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0045)
    - The Set Up, circa 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0157)
    - Steve Cannon: The Set Up / Chump Change / En Vogue, circa 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0141)
    - Too Short - I Want to be Free, circa 1992; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:04:23; Promotional Release (Jive Records, Silvertone Records).; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0052)
    - Butch Morris - Poet's Choir: Nuyorican 12-18-92, Whitney 12-31-92, Public Theatre 1-1-93, Nuyorican 2-11-93, Fez 3-9-93, 1992-1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0143)
    - Poets' Choir / 1st Night, 1992-1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label Annotations: "Whitney 12-31-92, Public 1-1-93"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0040)
    - Tribes at St. Mark's Church, January 29 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0056)
    - The Fez - Poet's Choir, Poets, Rappers, March 9 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:45:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0142)
    - Poet's Choir at the Fez, March 9 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0100)
    - Tribes at the Fez, April 11 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0160)
    - MCI Q3 SED Japanese / MCI Q3 SED Chinese/Mandarin / MCI Q3 SED Chinese/Cantonese, July 7 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:01:30; Original Format: 3/4 in. Umatic; Spine label: "Client: MCI; Tape Location: Black Hallway A; Tape Number: A10; Title: Q3 SED" (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0306)
    - Now What, What Now? Rehearsal, Show, August 18 & 20 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Steve Cannon, Butch Morris, Nick Video"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0081)
    - Now What, What Now? Rehearsal, Show, August 18 & 20, 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0156)
    - What Now, Now What, University Sts. / Tribes, Ham Fish Library, August 20 1993, April 8 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0055)
    - It's About Time: John Farris, September 12 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0010)
    - Nothing to Lose, October 21 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0035)
    - Tribes Meetings, December 7 & 21 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0069)
    - ABC News Nightline: Viewpoint: Crime, Violence and TV News, December 10 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial Release (MPI Home Video).; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0088)
    - What Now, Now What? Green Street 12-17-93 / Nuyorican 12-31-93, December 17 & 31 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0078)
    - What Now, Now What, December 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "What Now, Now What 12-17-93, 12-31-93"; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0036)
    - What Now, Now What - Tilden Gallery, December 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0075)
    - What Now, Now What - Tilden Gallery, December 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0080)
    - Longshot BK Party / What Now, Now What at Bobs / Tribes Discussion, circa 1993; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations similar in appearance to those on cassette 198.0075, which is dated 1993.; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0076)
    - Now What, What Now, April 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Tom's Copy"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0079)
    - Now What What Now? - Context, April 21 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon (c) 1994"; "cued for five minutes"; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0159)
    - Now What, What Now? by Steve Cannon, April 21 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0204)
    - Lee Liu & Tong: "Asian-American Heritage Month", April 22 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: 3/4 in. Umatic; Label: "Hi-8 Bump-Ups with Address Track"; "Hi-8 Burn-In T.C."; "Reel #2 Part 2"; "Studio Shoot / BMCC" (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0305)
    - Top of the World - Context, June 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0144)
    - Democracies in Chinatown: 1974-1994, circa 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0014)
    - Dora's Birthday / Kim's Caven, 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0099)
    - Tribes, Fish Library 10-15-94 / Gallery "Woodstock", 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0068)
    - Willem de Kooning: Artist, 1994; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Mystic Fire Video, Inc.). (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0024)
    - Cayenne: at Pyramid 1-22-94, Book Party 4-3-95, 1994-1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0101)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:05:00; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0093)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:05:00; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon"; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0121)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0139)
    - Top of the World - Nuyorican, March 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:06:00; Label annotation: "by Steve Cannon"; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0140)
    - I. Reed, T. Reed, & V.H. Cruz: Tribes Benefit, November 17 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0254)
    - I. Reed, T. Reed, & V.H. Cruz: Tribes Benefit, November 17 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0255)
    - Channel Zero: Planet Street, May 1995; 2 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 03:00:00; Commercial Release.; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0065)
      Currently no access copies are available.
    - Tribes Benefit, August 23 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Cassette sleeve annotation: "Xcluding The New Family & The Beaver's [Tail]"; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0113)
    - Victor Hernandez Cruz vs. A Gathering of the Tribes, December 2 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0077)
    - Gringo in Mananaland: A Musical, circa 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:01:16 Insert in cassette case with synopsis and quotations; Directed by Dee Dee Halleck.; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0147)
    - Poet's Choir, Context, 1995; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0097)
    - P-Town - 96 / Jan 7th - Tribes Knitting Factory, circa January 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0219)
    - Tribes - Nuyorican Poet's Cafe Part II, February 21 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0074)
    - Carlos at IBM Garden / Biblio-Poets, April 4 & 6, 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Carlos - 30 min."; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0058)
    - Tribes Art Opening, April 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0173)
    - Steve's Place - Hal's "Mother Said" Party / Star's "Waterworn", June 2 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 02:30:00; Label annotation: "by S.L. Fung"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0071)
    - Panel at Nuyorican Poets Cafe, July 14 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0044)
    - Pat Winter's "The Buzzing of Insects" at Nuyorican Poet's Cafe - 7/14/96 / Butch Morris' Poet's Chorus at Metro Pictures in Soho Arts Festival - 9/8/96 / Charlie Parker's Night - 8/28/96, July - September 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0046)
    - Film of Two Parties: Halloween '96 & Backyard, 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0151)
    - Knitting Factory: Sabir Mateen, Butch Morris, Jason Hwang, 1996; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotations: "Sabir Mateen 6/24/96, Butch Morris - Band 7/8/96, Jason Hwang - Alternit"; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0032)
    - Small Gems. Close to Closing., January 10 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0098)
    - Tribes at Gershwin Hotel, January 18 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0030)
    - Tribes Reading - Barnes and Noble, January 29 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Cam. Vipin"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0087)
    - Star Black, Tribes Gallery, March 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0057)
    - Tribes Benefit, April 25 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "Video - Dor Green". (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0027)
    - Sarah Jones @ Gershwin Hotel with Edwin Torres; Beau Sia; Kris Lew; Bob Holman; Everton Sylvester; Carman B. Brown & Hilcato with Musicians, May 18 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0085)
    - 1. Juma Santos' World Peace Drummers @ Gershwin 5/18/97 2. Tribes Gallery Show - Jim C 3. Ammiel Alcalay, Murat Nemet-Nejat, Sparrow @ Gershwin 6/5, May - June 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0111)
    - Silhouette @ Isart Gallery, Montreal; Featuring Designer Daniel Mistiva, July 10 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0176)
      Two postcard invitations removed from cassette sleeve and moved to Series III. They can be found in Box 17, Folder 29.
    - Suheir Hammad & John Farris 10/5/97 / Pedro Pietr1 10/12/97 at Ave B Social Club / Lorenzo Pace's "Triumph of the Human Spirit" 10/16/97 at African Burial Ground Breaking Ceremony with Giuliani, October 5, 12 & 16 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0086)
    - Eileen Weisman's "Off the Wall" / Remember These Nights... Ken McManus, Clara Sala, Letta Neely and David Morreale, at the Gershwin Hotel, 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0148)
    - Juma Santos - World Peace Drummers @ Gershwin Hotel 5/25/97 / Tribes Gallery Show - Jim Carl, 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:20:00; Label annotation: by Susan L. Yung.; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0114)
    - Silent Movie, 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:27:00; Commercial Release (20th Century Fox).; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0047)
    - Zero Point Zero Tape 1, April 25 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0163)
    - Zero Point Zero Tape 2, April 25 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0109)
    - The Charlie Parker Tribute, August 25 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0073)
    - Sheila's Birthday Party 9/26/98 / Anthony Murell's Tribes Opening, circa September 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0135)
    - Tribes: Exit Art NYU with Ishmael Reed / David Henderson Neo-Calif / Anthony Murrell 20 Class A Tobacco Suits / Elisabeth Atnafu East Village Universe, October - December 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0158)
    - Gathering of the Tribes Poetry Reading, October 2 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Handwritten container annotation: "Exit Art #8".; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0008)
    - Slyscrapers, Taxis & Tampax, November 15 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0170)
    - Backbone of the World, 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:56:06; By George Burdeau; Preview release (Independent Television Service).; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0134)
    - Kokoro no tabi - Shuntaro Tanikawa, 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "'98.5.2"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0066)
    - Tom Dent / A Reading Tribute, 1998; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0122)
    - "A Gathering of the Tribes" - The Public Theater, February 21 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0217)
    - Joe's Place, February 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0031)
    - Dallas Slam Team at Tribes, March 7 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0033)
      Currently no acces copy is available.
    - Dallas Slam Team at Tribes, March 7 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0108)
    - Poetry Project, Tape 1, April 11 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0193)
    - Peoples Poetry Gathering, Poetry Project, Tape 2, April 11 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS. (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0011)
    - Skyscrapers, Taxis & Tampons; Readings at Tribes & Thirteen, May 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0002)
    - March on Pentagon - Demonstrations in Washington, June 5 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Filmed by Dr. Ljubo Vujovic"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0042)
    - Tribes "Bird Nite" Tape 1 of 2, August 26 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:00:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0016)
    - Tribes "Bird Nite" Tape 2 of 2, August 26 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:27:00; Cassette annotation: "Bird Fest Tribes"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0067)
    - Earth Bird Presents: Poetry in the Garden, 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0112)
    - Skyscrapers, Taxis & Tampons, 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "video by [Murill]"; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0102)
    - Sweet Love, Bitter, 1999; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 01:32:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial Release (Rhapsody Films, Inc.). (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0029)
    - Ishmael Reed Reader March 30 / Morgan Stanley, John Farris 3/6/00, March 6 and 30 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0128)
    - Quincy Troupe - Tribes, April 2 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0127)
    - Cheryl Boyce Taylor at Tribes, April 30 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0050)
    - Bob H, Rax B, John Farris, Bobby G. - Opening at Tribes, May 6 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0126)
    - Staten Island Ferry / Hart Magazine Show, August 8 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 3, Cassette ID: 198.0107)
    - National Slam Festival, August 12 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0152)
    - Charlie Parker Festival, August 24 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0059)
    - Lorenzo Pace Sculpture Unveiling, October 19 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Recorded by Paul A. [Horea]"; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0209)
      Four 4x6 photos were separated from the cassette sleeve into Series III: Project Files.
    - Ute Schindler - Opening @ A Gathering of the Tribes, November 4 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0171)
    - Gathering of the Tribes Release Party, November 9 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Note attached to cassette sleve: "Tapes for Steve".; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0063)
    - Underground Fest @ Tribes Pt 1 & 2, November 11 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0180)
    - The Real Deal, 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:27:00; Commercial Release (The Cinema Guild, Inc.).; Label: "a short film about war written by Marc Levy".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0207)
    - Jazz on a Summer's Day, 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:30:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Bert Sterns Productions / New Yorker Films Artwork). (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0316)
    - Butch Morris: Global Fax Festival, circa 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0166)
    - Hettie Jones at Tribes / Underground Fest at Tribes Pt 3, circa 2000; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Cassette has same batch number as cassette 198.0063, which was dated 2000.; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0064)
    - Steve Cannon interview with Penny Arcade, February 27 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Note on cassette sleeve: "Interview that was made w/ Steve"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0037)
    - Clock, by Ron Keefer, April 16 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0249)
    - The Body of Loretta, April 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "Tribes, J. Liotta"; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0070)